这么说  这个娜奥米自从救你出炼狱
So, this "Naomi" has been controlling you
就一直在控制你
since she got you out of purgatory?
是
Yes.
你就是善心大发
So you just want to guide me out of purgatory
想带我离开炼狱吗
out of the goodness of your undead heart?
差不多吧
More or less.
你有什么好处
What's in it for you?
搭个顺风车
I'm hopping a ride.
什么
What?
那是个人类传送门  混蛋
It's a human portal, jackass.
仅限人类通过
Only humans can pass through.
他是个吸血鬼
He's a vampire.
多亏了他我才站在这儿
He's also the reason I'm topside.
我知道你在下面身不由己
I know you had to do what you had to down there.
但你已经出来了  本尼却还活着
But you're out now, and Benny's still breathing.
为什么
Why?
听着  本尼
Listen, Benny.
我永远不会忘记你为我做的一切
Everything you've done for me I will never forget.
就这样了
End of the line?
End of the line.
上帝建立了一系列测试
God built a series of tests.
等你都完成了  就可以去关门了
When you've done all three, you can slam the gates of hell.
萨姆  我没能通过测试
Sam, I didn't pass the test.
但是我通过了  剩下的都让我来
But I did. And I'm doing the rest of them.
-你得悠着点  -不行
- You got to slow down. - No.
你说要干掉地狱  那样我才能出去
You said nuking hell -- that's how I get out.
那样我才能回家
That's how I go home.
我想结束这件事
I need this to be over.
如今
凯文
Kevin.
我知道你在鼓捣什么
I know what you're up to...
跟温家兄弟合作
working with them, those Winchesters.
行不通的  凯文
Dead end, Kevin.
不在这儿
Not here.
也不在这儿
Not here, either.
别找了
Give up.
我在你脑子里  我无所不在
I'm in your head, as well as everywhere else.
你上次惹怒了我  丢了根指头
Last time you irked me, you lost a finger.
想想这次会怎么样
Imagine what will happen this time.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十九集
出租车司机
凯文  开门
Kevin, open up!
凯文
Kevin!
天呐  怎么回事  为什么发求救信号
Geez. What's going on? What's with the S.O.S.?
是他
It's him.
谁
It's who?
克劳力
Crowley.
他怎么了
What about him?
他在我脑子里
He's in my head.
你脑子里
He's...in your head.
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you know what that means?
知道  你的抗焦虑药得加量了
Yeah, it means we need to up your anxiety meds.
凯文  那是你的梦
Kevin, you're dreaming.
如果克劳力知道你在哪
Look, if Crowley knew where you were,
他就不会只折腾你的脑子了
he'd do a hell of a lot more than mess with your head.
盖思呢
All right, where's Garth?
去干活儿或者看牙医了  我不知道
On a case or -- or the dentist. I don't know.
我没有他的消息
I haven't heard from him.
好吧  你在电话上
Okay, well, what did you want to tell us
不肯说的是什么事
that you couldn't say on the phone?
你把煎锅放下行吗
Would you put the frying pan down, please?
我译出了石碑上第二道测试
I translated the second trial from the tablet.
你个疯狂的先知  干得好啊
You...crazy prophet, you. Nice work!
如果克劳力能进入我脑子  他也知道了
And if Crowley's in my head, he knows.
好吧  他绝对没有进入你的脑子
Okay, he's definitely not in your head.
他不在你脑子里  凯文
He's not in your head, Kevin.
没事的
It's okay. Just...
我们知道你压力很大  先跟我们说
We know you're distressed. Just stay with us, all right?
第二道测试是什么
What's the second trial?
从地狱拯救一个无辜的灵魂
An innocent soul has to be rescued from hell
并将它送入天堂
and delivered unto heaven.
什么
What?
"送入"  上帝就这么措辞
"Unto." That's -- that's how God talks.
拯救地狱里的灵魂  要下地狱吗
Rescue a soul from hell? Like actually...go to hell?
要怎么将灵魂送入天堂
How -- how do you get a soul unto heaven?
要怎么将灵魂弄出地狱啊
I mean, how do you even get a soul out of hell?
我们需要找个专家
We're gonna need an expert.
温家兄弟
Winchesters.
那个性感的小妞呢
What happened to the hot chicks?
我走了
I'm out of here.
我看不行
Maybe not.
我什么都没有
I ain't got nothing.
去死吧
Bite me.
那就再来一下吧
Well, then how about another owie?
你告诉我们要怎么偷偷下地狱
You know, wouldn't it be a lot easier just to tell us
不是简单多了
how to enter hell, uh, uninvited?
那是个秘密
It's...a secret.
我们保证不说出去
We promise we won't tell anyone.
不  等等  我不能
No! Wait. I can't.
那是禁忌
It's forbidden, man.
他们会杀了我的
They're gonna kill me.
求你了
Please...
好吧
All right, look...
只要价钱合适  你们都能偷渡进入地狱
For a price, y'all can be smuggled across hell's border.
-找谁  -野死神
- By who? - Rogue reapers.
他们有进出的秘密方法
They got secret ways, in and out.
不仅是地狱  膈幕  天堂
Not just hell -- the veil, heaven.
野死神偷渡人吗
Rogue reapers smuggling people?
人  灵魂
People, souls...
怎么  他们是地狱的蛇头吗
So, what? They're like hell coyotes?
杀了我吧  求你了
Now kill me. Come on, man.
死了也比被克劳力收拾强
Better death than Crowley.
有道理
Hmm. Good point.
但你得先告诉我们
But first you're gonna tell us...
一切
everything.
阿杰
Ajay.
我们要跟你谈谈
Need to talk to you for a sec.
你们知道我的名字
You know my name.
和你的生意
And what you do.
我们是来谈生意的
We want to do business.
但你们是凡人  血肉之躯
But you are mortal -- flesh and blood.
但如果我们想穿越地狱之界
But if we wanted to cross the border into hell --
进去看看
Visitor's pass.
没人想进地狱
No one wants to get into hell.
但你这样的蛇头能帮我们吗
But could a coyote like you do it?
是可能的
It's possible.
但我有特别的技能
But I have special skills.
我的费用可不小
I have overhead. It will be pricy.
多少钱
How pricey?
你们那么聪明
You two are resourceful.
有一天  你们会欠我一个人情
One day, you will owe me a favor.
你说的好像你认识我们
You say that like you know us.
当然了  你们是温家兄弟
Of course. You're the Winchesters.
抱歉  我们见过吗
Sorry. Have we met?
我是把鲍比・辛格带入地狱的死神
I am the reaper who took Bobby Singer to hell.
鲍比在地狱
Bobby in hell?
我们烧了他的骨头  那样就都结束了
We burned his bones. Once we did that, it was over.
没有然后了
End of story.
那可未必
Not necessarily.
不不不  鲍比是个好人
No, no, no, 'cause, see, Bobby was on the good side of things,
好人是要上阁楼的
and good guys go to the penthouse.
一般是如此
Usually, mostly.
这要看你认识谁  谁来处理你了
Depends on who you know, what palms get greased.
如果你上了地狱之王的黑名单
If you're on the king of hell's no-fly list,
就别想上天堂了
no way you cruise the friendly skies.
是克劳力
Crowley.
好吧  那就这样
Okay, let's do this.
两张下行票和三张上行票是多少钱
How much for two tickets down and three back?
-迪恩  -怎么了
- Dean. - What?
过来一下
Come here.
你怎么想的啊
What the hell are you thinking?
你听到他的话了  鲍比在地狱
You heard the guy -- Bobby's in hell.
我们得去救他
We're gonna spring him.
这我们谈过了  迪恩  我得独自完成测试
We've gone over this, Dean. I have to do the trials solo.
这可是鲍比啊  萨姆
This is Bobby we're talking about, Sam.
我们说实话吧
Now let's face it --
你最近状态并不算很好
you have not exactly been up to full speed lately, okay?
我们有这个机会  我们不能有失误
We got one shot at this. We can't miss.
不会有失误的
I'm not gonna miss.
我会把他带回来的
I'll bring him back.
我去  我一个人
I'm in, just me.
跟我来
Follow me.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
这到底是怎么个运作方式
How does this...work?
别担心
Not to fret.
他整整一天后就会回来
He'll be back in exactly 24 hours time.
你可以到时来找他
Return for him then.
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
越来越恶心了
And it gets creepier.
这就是地狱吗
So, this is hell?
不  这是炼狱
Not at all. This is purgatory.
你说这是炼狱是什么意思
What do you mean this is purgatory?
我要的不是这个  我要去的是地狱
This isn't what I paid for. I booked the hell tour.
温彻斯特  别激动啊
Whoa, whoa, Winchester, detach.
这里离地狱很近
This is hell-adjacent.
这条路我走了很多次了
Been down this highway many times before.
沿着小溪  走到三棵树融为一体的地方
Follow the stream to where three trees meet as one.
那里有石头
Where they meet, there are rocks.
石头之间是道传送门
Between the rocks is the portal.
传送门
A portal?
进入地狱的后门
A back door to hell.
相信我  能行的
Trust me -- it'll work.
等等  你不跟我一起来吗
Wait. So you're not coming with me?
别傻了
Don't be ridiculous.
把一个凡人偷渡过来就够冒险的了
Smuggling a mortal across the border is risky enough.
把一个温家兄弟带进地狱  可得要命了
But gate-crashing a Winchester into hell seriously blows.
不  我整一天之后回来
No. I'll be back in 24 hours, precisely.
在这儿等着我
Be here.
你幸好带了那个来
It's a good thing you brought that.
这里可不好混
It is not an easy place.
凯文  是我
Yo, Kev, it's me!
凯文
Kevin.
我觉得柜子是最安全的
I believe the closet would be safest.
你怕什么
Safe from what?
克劳力
Crowley.
他钻进了我的脑子  迪恩
He's in my head, Dean.
那样的话  他就知道我的位置
And if he's in my head, he knows where I am!
我们应该搬走
You know, we -- we should move out.
再找个地方
We'll find another place.
凯文  你冷静点好吗
Geez, Kev, would you chill out, huh?
来个汉堡
Have a burger.
行了  别现在发疯啊  老兄
Come on. Don't lose it on me now, dude.
这就对了
There you go. That's it.
这些都结束了告诉我
Just tell me when this all ends,
我只想听到那个
'cause that's the only thing I want to hear.
我之前说过了  这是不会结束的
No, like I told you before, this isn't going to end.
听我说   其他人的生活很简单
Look, man, other guys, they got it easy, you know?
在后院烧烤  参加保龄球队
It's all backyard barbecues and...bowling teams,
但是我们要额外承担一些事
but you and me? We got to carry a little extra weight.
我承担不了
I can't take it.
你当然能
Yes, you can.
看着我
Hey, look at me.
我知道这一切都很糟糕
Now, this whole thing sucks. I know.
但你得承受
But you suck it up
并且扛过去  我们就得这样
and you push through because that's what we do.
一旦你接受了这个
And when you get on board with that,
就会好过多了
the ride is a lot smoother.
要薯条吗
French fry?
我去屋里了
I'm gonna -- I'm gonna be in my room.
哪天情况转好再告诉我
Let me know when there's a good day.
那是我的馅饼
That's my pie.
你好啊  阿杰
Hello, Ajay.
我们很久没聊天了
It's been a while since we chatted --
太久了
too long.
来点披萨
Pizza?
加了凤尾鱼
Extra anchovies.
有什么事想跟我说说吗
Anything you want to get off your chest?
新情况
An update?
没有啊
Um...no.
没什么
No, not really.
你或许记得  我这人耐性不太好
As you may recall, patience isn't one of my virtues.
说实话  我这人总体来说不怎么好
Well, I don't have any virtues, but if I did,
但就算我有优点也不会是有耐性
I'm certain that patience wouldn't be one.
那么  你真的没什么想说的吗
So, sure there's nothing weighing on you?
比如  跟温家兄弟做交易
Nothing, say, about making a deal with the Winchesters?
先生  我知道那种事做不得
Sir, I know better than to attempt that.
我的探子看见你跟萨姆・温彻斯特一起离开
My operative saw you leaving with Sam Winchester.
萨姆・温彻斯特啊
Oh! Oh, Sam Winchester.
是啊
Oh, yes, that's, uh...
有这可能
A possibility.
你在考验我本来就没有的耐性
You're trying my non-patience.
先生  我只是在做自己的生意
Sir, I was just doing what I do.
您也知道
As you are more than aware,
我有时候  会兼职做点小生意
I do occasionally -- moonlight as a freelancer.
你不能跟他们做生意
You do not freelance with them.
萨姆想要什么
What did Sam want?
其实  我现在想起来了
Well, uh, actually, it's, uh, starting to come back.
他好像想进地狱
He may have wanted to get into hell.
我的地狱  他为什么要那么做
My hell? Why would he want to do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我发誓  干我这行  我不多问的
I swear. My job -- I don't ask questions.
那么温彻斯特先生什么时候从地狱回来
And what time is Mr. Winchester due back from hell?
我接他的时间是
Uh, I'm picking him up in...
17小时之后
well, now 17 hours.
我知道了  还有吗
I see. Anything else?
没了
No.
我发誓
I swear.
这趟辛苦费你别想收了
That's one fare you won't be collecting.
是个兔子洞  真是疯了
It's a rabbit hole. This is nuts.
我是无辜的
I'm...innocent.
帮帮我
Help me.
艾迪   艾迪
Eddy? Eddy?
艾迪  艾迪
你来了
You came.
我就知道你会的
I knew you would.
我一直在为此祈祷
I've been praying for it forever.
我不是他  对不起
I'm not...him. I'm sorry.
你来了
You came.
我就知道你会的
I knew you would.
我一直在为此祈祷
I've been praying for it. Forever.
你来了  我就知道你会的
You came. I knew you would.
我一直在为此祈祷
I've been praying for it forever.
鲍比
Bobby?
给我滚出去  你个黑眼混蛋
Get the hell out of here, you black-eyed son of a bitch.
什么  鲍比  我是萨姆啊
What? Bobby, it's Sam.
我还是猫王呢  给我走开
Yeah, and I'm Elvis. Move your ass!
-鲍比  -给我滚
- Bobby - - Get!
是我啊
It's me!
该死  如果不是萨姆
Okay, damn it. If it's not Sam...
那我怎么知道你和托瑞・斯培林的事
Then how do I know all about you and Tori Spelling?
美国女演员
什么
What?
我知道你粉她  还有
You're a fan. Yeah. Or -- or, uh...
还有你在美国商城免费修脚的事
Okay. What about your free pedicure at the Mall of America?
你逼迪恩永远不许告诉别人
You made Dean swear to never tell another living soul
这事对你人生的改变
how it changed your life.
萨姆
Sam?
对不起  萨姆
I'm sorry, Sam,
但你之前都来过两百个萨姆了
But you're the 200th Sam I've seen today.
他们就这么折磨我
That's how they screw with me.
总有各种黑眼的萨姆和迪恩来
Just endless Sams and Deans all wearing the same black eyes.
等等
Wait a minute.
你怎么会在这儿
What the hell are you doing here?
别告诉我是我想的那样
Please don't tell me it's what I think it is.
不不  鲍比  我没事
No, no, no, Bobby, I'm good. I...
我是来救你的
I'm here to get you.
你不该待在这儿  鲍比
You don't belong here, Bobby.
我们要救你出去
And we're getting you out.
难道只有我一人理解情况有多紧急吗
Am I the only one who sees the urgency of this situation?
-先生  -这里面绝对有问题
- Sir - - Something is going on.
我的地狱之犬被杀
My hellhound has been killed.
大号温彻斯特想要闯进我的母舰
Winchester jumbo size is trying to break into the mother ship.
他们那个先知在疯狂地翻译
And that prophet of theirs is madly translating away.
自己算算
Add it up!
我会的  先生
I will, sir.
你是哪来的  临时雇员中介吗
Where did we get you, huh? Temp agency?
我要凯文・谭和他那半的石碑
I need Kevin Tran, and I need his half of the tablet.
显然好东西都在他那半上
Apparently, his half has the good stuff,
而我那半只有致谢和作者简介
where mine has the acknowledgements and "about the author."
会搞定的
It will be done.
那是最好了
It had better be.
找到那个孩子
Find that kid.
凯文
Hey, Kevin!
过来吃点鸡蛋
Come in here and grab some of these eggs.
凯文  你不能永远躲在里面啊
Kev! Come on, man. You can't hide in there forever.
你去哪了
Where the hell you been?
你不是正怕着呢吗
What happened to being scared?
我是怕
I am scared.
所以我先采取了行动
So I made a preemptive move.
什么
So...
你做了什么
Made a what now?
我不能捧着块石碑坐在这儿
I can't sit here with the tablet like a...
像个活靶子被克劳力死死盯着
sitting duck and Crowley breathing down my ass.
把石碑丢掉能减轻点压力
Getting rid of the tablet just takes off some of the pressure.
等等  丢掉
Wait. Getting rid of it?
只是暂时的  我藏起来了
Temporarily. I hid it.
什么  藏哪了
What? Where?
我要是告诉你藏哪了就不叫藏了
If I tell you where, it's not hidden, is it?
凯文  告诉我石碑藏哪了  否则我...
Kevin, tell me where the damn tablet is, or I swear to you --
你能怎么样  迪恩
You'll what, Dean?
凯文
Kevin!
孩子啊  小时候真可爱
Kids. So cute when they're little.
一变成青少年就烦人了
Then they turn into teenagers, and the party's over.
我们还没正式见过  迪恩
We haven't been formally introduced, Dean.
我叫娜奥米
My name is Naomi.
我知道你是谁
Oh, I know who you are.
我知道小卡离开炼狱后你对他做了什么
And I know what you did to Cass after he got out of purgatory.
你是说我把他救出了炼狱之后
After I rescued him from purgatory, you mean,
而且为此牺牲了好几个天使
at the cost of many angels' lives.
你折腾他的脑子  让他监视我们
You screwed with his head and had him spy on us.
我的确跟卡西迪奥谈过很多次
Well, it is true that I have spoken with Castiel many times,
我那是想接触他  帮他
trying to reach out to him, trying to help him.
迪恩  你肯定注意到了炼狱对他的改变
Dean, you must have noticed how purgatory changed him.
他过去也曾不稳定
I mean, he's been unstable in the past,
但我对他现在的伤还是很震惊
but I was shocked at how damaged he is now.
行了  别想把这事洗白了
Stop, okay? Don't -- don't try to spin this.
你以为我不知道你让他杀我吗
You think I don't know that you told him to try and kill me?
我想在他听来就是那个意思了
Yeah, I suppose that is how he would hear it.
我得知天使石碑时
When I learned of the angel tablet,
我的确让卡西迪奥不惜任何代价得到它
I did tell Castiel to get it at any cost.
那是我的工作  保护天堂
That's my job -- to protect heaven.
我跟你一样  是个战士
I'm a warrior, just as you are.
你觉得我该怎么样
What would you expect?
而现在卡西迪奥不知去向
And now Castiel is in the wind
兜里还揣着个氢弹
with a hydrogen bomb in his pocket,
我怕我们都会有危险
and I -- I'm scared, for all of us.
省省吧
Save it.
我不信任天使  所以我不信任你
See, I don't trust angels, which means I don't trust you.
但你却没给这里施加天使防护咒
And yet you haven't warded this place against us.
我知道
I know.
你希望卡西迪奥会回来
You're hoping Castiel will return to you.
我敬重你的忠诚
I admire your loyalty.
真希望他也能如此
I only wish he felt the same way.
我知道你不愿相信  迪恩
I know you don't want to believe it, Dean,
但我们是一边的  关闭地狱之门
but we're on the same side -- shutting the gates of hell,
让卡西迪奥归群
bringing Castiel in from the cold.
想想吧
Take a moment.
考虑我的话
Think about what I've said.
我知道你们跟阿杰做了生意
I know you've been doing business with Ajay.
他提到了吧
He did mention, didn't he,
他进入地狱的路径要途径炼狱
that his way into hell is through purgatory?
我想你会想知道
I knew you'd want to know.
你看  我们能彼此帮助的
You see, we can be of help to each other.
你心里有数吗
You know where the hell you're going?
我们就到了
Yeah, we're almost there.
后退  后退
Get back. Get back, get back.
走吧  我们出去
Let's go! We got to get out of here!
鲍比  他们在迷惑你
Bobby, they're messing with you.
别听他的  他不是真的
Don't listen to him. He's not real.
-鲍比  离他远点  -我们得走了
- Bobby, get away from him! - We got to go now -- aah!
你心里是知道的  对吧
You knew somehow, right?
赌了一把
Took a chance.
一半一半嘛
50/50.
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
瞧啊
Look, look.
阿杰
Ajay? Hey.
这是什么地方
What the hell is this?
好吧  别生气
All right, don't get all pissed off.
是炼狱
Purgatory.
该死
Balls!
走吧
Let's go.
是我
Yeah. Hey, it's me.
我知道
I know.
我知道  很久没联系了
I know, man. It's been a long time.
我也想打给你  只是...
I mean, I wanted to call. I did. I just, uh...
觉得还是不打为好
I thought it might be better if I didn't.
很高兴听到你的声音  迪恩
So good to hear your voice, Dean.
真心的
I mean that.
你还好吗
How you been?
你知道的
Oh, you know...
我还好吧
I get by.
我让你失望了吧
I guess I let you down, huh?
你能打来我很高兴
I'm just happy as hell to hear from you.
过会儿你大概就不这么想了
You might change your mind about that.
什么意思
Why? What you mean?
本尼  我得求你件事
Benny, I got to ask you a favor.
大事
It's a big one.
这道测试之后还有几道
So, how many more of these trials after this?
只有一道了
Just one.
但是还不知道是什么
Don't know what it is, though -- not yet.
凯文还在翻译
Kevin's still translating.
你刚刚在地狱里也看到了  我还能活动
Well, you saw back there in hell, I ain't got a lot of rust.
能再次参与行动感觉真好
Just feels so good to be back in action again.
如果我跟在你们身边或许能帮上忙
Might be handy if you had me around to help.
鲍比  相信我  我也想
Bobby, I'd -- I'd love that, believe me.
但是  要完成测试
The thing is, for this trial to be completed,
你的灵魂要进入天堂
your soul has to enter heaven.
而且  如果不那样
And besides, if that weren't the case,
我们都烧了你的尸骨了  鲍比
we burned your bones, Bobby.
在地上也没有能承载你灵魂的东西
There's nothing to tie your spirit to earth.
好吧
Yeah. Yeah, well...
我一直以为那样就完了
You know, I always figured that'd be the end of it...
猎人葬礼
You know, just a hunter's funeral.
就什么都不剩了
Zip. Nothing.
那我也没意见
And I was okay with that.
所以这真是没想到
Imagine my surprise.
如果非得有永生
Well, I guess if there has to be an eternity,
我宁可上天堂也好过下地狱
I'd pick heaven over hell.
是啊  因为上边就天下太平了
Yeah. 'cause there's nothing screwy going on up there.
真希望这我能说了算
I wish I made the rules.
嗯
Well...
我就做我该做的  了结这事
I'll, uh, do my part, get to the end of this, but...
我可不是退休的那种人
I ain't exactly the retiring type,
所以如果你们两个白痴能让我还魂
so, you idjits figure out a way to spring me...
当然了  这没问题
Yeah. No, of course. That's, uh -- yeah.
我们上去吧
Oh, well, let's get topside.
怎么了  萨姆
What's going on, Sam?
就是这里  肯定就是这儿
This is it. This is the place. I'm sure of it.
你出租车司机应该在这里等你吗
Where your cabbie's supposed to meet you?
对  就是现在
Yeah. At exactly...now.
那么他来晚了
So, he's running a little late.
不  是这样的
No, see, that's the thing.
鲍比  他明确说过要一分不差
He was very specific, Bobby, like, to the minute.
如果他没出现
And if he doesn't show...?
我们就没法出去了
We got no way out.
你要是不想插手
If you want nothing to do with this,
我完全理解
I completely understand.
迪恩・温彻斯特要帮忙  可不是胡闹的
When Dean Winchester asks for a favor, he's not screwing around.
本尼  让你去那里
Benny, sending you back there
是我最不想做的事情
is the last thing I ever wanted to do.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
但是我弟弟困在里面了
But my little brother is stuck down there.
就是那个要杀了我的弟弟  是吗
This would be the little brother who wants to kill me, right?
你可以进去
You got access to the place.
你说"进去"  是指"身首异处"
By "Access," You mean "Getting beheaded"?
对  你说得对  我要求的太过分了
Yeah, you're right -- it's too much.
最近我也没为你做什么
It's not like I've exactly been there for you lately.
什么
What?
别这样  迪恩
Oh, come on, Dean.
你知道我喜欢挑战
You know I love a challenge.
你是说真的
You're serious?
他可是你弟弟
Hey, he's your brother.
我们开始吧
I say let's do this.
我欠你的
I owe you.
你什么都不欠我
Oh, you don't owe me nothing.
事实是
Truth is, uh...
我正好可以借此休息一下
I could use a break from all this.
真的那么艰辛吗
It really been that tough?
迪恩  我无法融入群体
I'm not a good fit, Dean.
和吸血鬼不行  和人类当然更不行
Not with vampires and, for sure, not with the humans.
我不属于任何一方
I don't belong.
过了一阵后
And after a while...
这种感觉令人厌烦
That starts to wear on you.
真是的
Right?
好像你需要听我唧唧歪歪似的
Cry me a river. Like you need to listen to this.
等你回到这里
Well, when you get back up here,
我们一起想办法好吗
we're gonna fix all that, okay?
等我回来
When I get back?
对  你找到传送门
Yeah, you find the portal,
跟萨姆一起离开炼狱
and your ride out of purgatory with Sam
就像以前我们那样
just like you did with me, okay?
我一送你回去
As soon as I send you back,
我就立刻赶往缅因州
I'm gonna haul my ass up to Maine,
你们出来时  我就在那里等着你们
and I'm gonna be waiting there for you when you get topside.
好啊  这听起来挺靠谱的
Yeah. That sounds like a plan, chief.
我们开始吧
Let's get on with it.
你确定要做吗
You sure about this?
又不是我第一次了
Not my first rodeo, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧  你个懦夫
Well, come on. You a wimp?
迪恩在这里待了一年吗
Dean spent a year in this place?
边逃边战斗  从早到晚  每一天
Running and fighting, all day, every day.
那段时间
Must have been hell on you
你不能救他出来  一定很难过吧
not being able to get him out all that time.
你试着救他了吧
You did try?
鲍比  迪恩和我之前说好了
Look, Bobby, Dean and I had an agreement, okay?
我知道
I know that agreement.
那是我教你们的
I taught you that agreement.
那是你们不会遵守的约定
That's a non-agreement.
我感觉我离开后一定发生了许多事
I get the feeling a lot must have happened while I was gone.
萨姆
Sam!
鲍比  不不  等等
Bobby, no, no, wait! Wait! Wait!
你怎么在这里
Why are you here?
迪恩让我来的
Dean sent me.
迪恩  不会是我的迪恩
Dean? Not my Dean.
他是迪恩的朋友  鲍比
He's a buddy of Dean's, Bobby.
朋友
A buddy?
好朋友
A good buddy.
一个该死的吸血鬼
A frigging vampire?
我走后你俩真是
Well, you two really went off the rails
什么都敢做啊
while I was gone, didn't you?
本尼  听着  我知道你曾在这里
Hey, Benny, listen -- I know you saved my brother's ass
多次救过我哥  我很感激
a few times down here, and I respect that.
对  我现在是想救你们
Yeah, and now I'm trying to save yours.
知道吗  我真是给吸血鬼丢脸
You know, I'm a disgrace to my own people.
对  就是这里
Yeah, this is the spot.
能让我们上去的缝隙
The seam that gets us back up top?
是那个吗
Is that it?
对  是的
Yeah, that's it.
你们记得我说的话吗
You boys remember what I told you?
记得
Yeah.
好了  鲍比  现在这样
All right, Bobby, here it goes.
我上去后  就放你出去
When we get to earth and I release you,
你就能直入天堂
it's an express straight to heaven.
没时间道别
No time for goodbyes.
已经和你道别过一次了  萨姆
Already said goodbye to you once, Sam.
也没什么了不起的
Didn't seem to take.
我今后说不定
No reason to think I won't see you again
还能再见到你
somewhere down the road.
是啊
Yeah.
可如果上面让我坐安乐椅
But if they give me a rocking chair up there,
我一定会破口大骂
I'm raising hell.
[咒语]
Conjuncti sumus, unum sumus.
好了  来吧  本尼  该你了
All right. Come on, Benny. It's your turn.
快点
Hurry up.
本尼
Benny.
还和温家兄弟合作呢
And still working with the Winchesters.
快点
Hurry.
萨姆  你该走了
Time for you to go, Sam.
本尼
Benny?
走吧  他们想要我  你走吧
Go on. It's me they want. Go on.
你只要告诉迪恩  我说再见
You just make sure you tell Dean I said goodbye.
我在那边本来也过不好
I was never any good up there anyway.
本尼  等等
Benny, wait!
本尼
Benny?
缅因州  100英里荒地
炼狱啊
Purgatory, right?
真是个园艺场  是吧
A real garden spot, ain't it?
是啊
Yeah.
你把他带出来了吗
Did you get him out?
只带出了鲍比
Only Bobby.
什么
What?
带出鲍比太好了
I mean, that's fantastic about Bobby.
迪恩  听着  本尼
Dean, look -- Benny, uh...
是他带我们出来的
He got us out.
出现了几个吸血鬼  他把他们引开了
A bunch of vamps showed, and he used himself as bait.
我感觉即使没有吸血鬼来
I get the feeling that even if that didn't happen,
他也不想回来  你知道吗
he didn't want to come back, you know?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
也许你是对的
You're probably right.
那么  鲍比  他在那下面还好吗
So, uh...Bobby -- how -- how'd he hold up down there?
鉴于种种情况  他还好了
He's good, all things considered.
当然了  脾气大得很
Ornery as hell, of course.
他就该这样
As he should be.
我们送那个老人家去他该去的地方吧
Let's put that old man where he belongs.
好
Yeah.
[咒语]
Solvo haec phantasmata in terram,
Et inde ad olympum.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
孩子们  你们好
Hello, boys.
鲍比・辛格  化成烟我也认识
Bobby Singer -- I'd know you anywhere.
放他走  克劳力
Let him go, Crowley.
他不属于地狱
He doesn't belong in hell.
我说是就是
He does if I say he does.
他曾给我族类带来无数伤害
He's inflicted untold damage on my kind.
要我说
From where I sit,
他连下地狱都不配
actually, hell's too good for him.
不是吧
Really?
怎么回事
What?
不是吧
Oh, come on!
我看看我对目前情况的理解是否正确
Let me see if I've interpreted the situation correctly.
温家兄弟从地狱救出了一个无辜的人
The Winchesters have freed an innocent from hell,
而你却在阻挠他的升天
to which you are wrongfully trying to return it.
和他们一伙儿了吗  娜奥米
Siding with them, Naomi?
你可不了解他们俩
You don't know those two.
他们会把我们都关起来
Before they're done, we'll both be locked away.
亲爱的  我只希望他们把你关起来
I'm just hoping they lock you away, dear.
别的我自有办法
The rest I'll figure out.
你个官僚
Bureaucrat.
你这是自不量力
You're fighting outside your weight class.
不许说我是官僚
Don't call me a bureaucrat.
我说过你可以信任我
I told you you could trust me.
那是什么意思
What the hell was that about?
我等会儿告诉你  先完成测试
I'll tell you later. Let's get this trial done.
[咒语]
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
萨姆
Sam?
怎么了
What? What?!
告诉我  怎么了
Talk to me! What?!
没事  没事
It's okay! It's okay!
没事  我没事
It's okay. I'm fine.
做完了
It's done.
真是玩腻了  不是吗  凯文
So tired of this, aren't you, Kevin?
恐惧  躲藏
Fear, the hiding.
我是玩腻了
I know I am.
这只是一场梦
Just a dream.
我只是在做梦
It's just a dream.
凯文・谭
Kevin Tran.
好久不见
It's been a while.
以为你能躲我一辈子吗
Thought you could elude me forever?
总是有办法的
There's always a way.
如果找不到这个谭  就去找另一个谭
If you can't find one Tran, find another.
你妈妈不愿透露你的下落
Your mom, she didn't want to give you up.
她真能忍啊
Quite a pain threshold, that one.
但她能承受的痛苦也是有限的
But even she could only take so much.
她不可能告诉你的
She never would have told you.
当妈的都那样  不是吗
Moms are like that, aren't they?
所以我们杀了她
So we killed her
从她手机里找到了你的地址
and got your address off her smartphone.
不
No!!
你们这些人永远都不理解
What you people never seem to understand
你们什么都不是
is that you are nothing!
你们只是转瞬即逝的灯光
Fleeting blips of light.
而我永垂不朽
I am forever.
你没事吧
You okay?
我把本尼埋了
I buried Benny...
但我没有烧掉他的尸体
...but I didn't burn his bones.
毕竟他努力救了你们
After he said he'd try to get you out of there,
我不忍心放弃他
it just didn't seem right.
我知道你瞧不上他  但是
I know you got no use for him, but..
不不  你知道吗
No, no, no. You know what?
其实我懂  真的
I get it. I do.
他和我想的并不一样
He's a... He's a little different from what I thought.
你想留着他就留吧
So, go ahead and leave the door open if you want.
好吧  咱们去看看先知小子
All right, well, let's go check in with prophet boy
搞清楚他把石碑藏在了哪
and see where he stashed that tablet.
凯文  是我们
Kevin? It's us.
凯文
Kevin!
Kevin?
他不见了
He's gone.
他拿走了我们所有的东西  他的笔记
He took all our stuff, his notes...
我就知道  他终于还是吓傻了
I saw this coming. Finally freaked.
小毛孩逃了
Little geek made a run for it.
是啊  但他会去哪
Yeah, but where?